

Satguru Saran Satsangi P.

UI / UX designer | Product Designer | Researcher



🦯 satsangi77@gmail.com



Fremont, California
Open to move



+13177021793



04/04/1993



psssatsangi.com



Hello, I'm Saran. I love being creative, exploring and broadening my horizons, doing things in high quality and giving stunning user experience in my products. I'm enthusiast of user experience design and product design. I am also a business oriented person with good knowledge in business model and value map.

Experiences

October 2017 - Present

UI/UX Designer New Wisdom, LLC

January 2017 - Present

Graduate Research Assistant

Comet Lab SoIC, IUPUI

June 2014 – July 2014 (Internship)

Web Designer

The Workshop

Cairo, Egypt

Education

January 2017 - Present

MS Human Computer Interaction

Indiana University, Indianapolis

August 2011 - May 2016

B.Tech. Information Technology

Gayatri Vidya Parishad college of Engineering

Projects

August 2017 - October 2017

IOT in Kitchen (GE Appliances design challenge)

Group project (Role: Operations Manager)
We designed IOT product and service based business incorparating Meal Orchestration, Health and Delivery services.

October 2017 – November 2017

"Ava" The next step to InfoLink

(Crown Equipments design challenge)

Group project (Role: Design Manager)
We designed a new application for fleet management,
and also designed a Augmented Reality concept for
warehouse managers to monitor and check data and
performance.

October 2017 - Present

Virtual Try-on

(Role: UI/UX Designer)

Integrated virtual try-on into a Ecom website of a brand. Also worked on designing the UI of the VTO.

August 2017 – October 2017

Amazon Prime Kitchen (Amazon design challenge)

Group project (Role: Product Manager)

We designed a novel automated delivery system to deliver healthy and fresh food in a hassle free and optimized way.

Tools

Mac OS X Sketch Balsamiq Adobe Creative Suite Github

Design Skills

Mobile design
Prototyping
Web designing
UI design
UX design
Illustration
Photography
Animation



References

Robert Skipworth Comer, M.S.

Research Associate, Media Arts and Science

Sonny E. Kirkley

Adjunct Assistant Professor